whohauntsneil.com 2017-10-17

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - Who Haunts Neil

## Privacy Policy:

WhoHauntsNeil.com (" **MD Media** ") operates WhoHauntsNeil.com and may operate other websites. It is MD Media's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, MD Media collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MD Media's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MD Media's visitors use its website. From time to time, MD Media may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

MD Media also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WhoHauntsNeil.com blogs/sites. MD Media only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to MD Media's websites choose to interact with MD Media in ways that require MD Media to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that MD Media gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [WhoHauntsNeil.com](http://www.whohauntsneil.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with MD Media are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, MD Media collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with MD Media. MD Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

MD Media may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. MD Media may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, MD Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

MD Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MD Media's behalf or to provide services available at MD Media's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using MD Media's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MD Media will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, MD Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when MD Media believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MD Media, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an MD Media website and have supplied your email address, MD Media may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with MD Media and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MD Media takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MD Media uses cookies to help MD Media identify and track visitors, their usage of MD Media website, and their website access preferences. MD Media visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using MD Media's websites, with the drawback that certain features of MD Media's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If MD Media, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that MD Media goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MD Media may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MD Media and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, MD Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MD Media's sole discretion. MD Media encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WhoHauntsNeil.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Disclaimer**

WhoHauntsNeil.com essentially focuses on helping its viewers acquire profound knowledge in the field of Apps.

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by MD Media and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of MD Media. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, MD Media takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
